badrairlines.com 2015-04-23

# Privacy Policy

Badr Ailrlines is committed to protecting the privacy of information you provide us on this website. This policy explains how we collect and use customer information and how we protect your privacy.

This policy is applicable to Badr Ailrlines website only and does not cover any access you make to third party sites, even while using links from our Badr Ailrlines website.

1\. Why do we ask for personal information?  
2\. How do we use your personal information?  
3\. Disclosure of your personal information  
4\. Cookies  
5\. Site tracking  
6\. Security  
7\. Consent1.    1\. Why do we ask for personal information?

The personal information we request is necessary to allow us to process your flight booking. It is also required to register you on our website. Such information includes, but not limited to: name, family names, mailing addresses, telephone numbers, email addresses, billing addresses, credit or debit card numbers, expiry dates, and security numbers. 

If you are making a booking on behalf of another person, make sure that you have gained their consent to divulge such information. It is possible that such information may be globally processed.

2.    2\. How do we use your personal information?

Our airline will use your information to provide and personalise our service. We will also use your contact details to communicate with you. We may use your information to send you special offers, travel deals, and news about 

Badr Ailrlines products and services or those of relevant companies which we think may be of interest to you. We may contact you by post, email, telephone (including SMS) or fax for these purposes. We may also use and analyse the information that we collect so that we can review, administer, support, improve, and develop our business and services.  
  
3.    Disclosure of your personal informationBadr Ailrlines will not share or trade your personal information to third parties unless in case of emergency or when required by law.Badr Ailrlines may only share your personal information to the extent required for the performance of activities such as:   

  * to make an air travel reservation,   

  * to record and issue a ticket,   

  * to issue a boarding pass,   

  * for other purposes associated with or incidental to your carriage [Conditions of Carriage],   

  * to facilitate related transactions to your journey, such as car hire or hotel accommodation,   

  * to customs and/or immigration departments or other regulatory authorities in your country of departure and/or destination in order to comply with the laws in those countries, and   

  * to our employees and agents to execute any of the aforementioned points on our behalf. 

4.    Cookies

A ‘cookie’ is a small bit of data used by a browser to store information. These enable 

Badr Ailrlines to provide you with more personalised services on any future bookings. Cookies can be deleted from your hard drive if you wish. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can change your browser settings to prevent this option. Even without a cookie you can use most of the features on our website. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information.5.    Site Tracking

We use tracking software to monitor customer traffic patterns and site usage to help us develop the design and layout of our website. This software does not enable us to capture any personally identifying information.

6.    Security

We take great care to ensure the security of this site.

Badr Ailrlines uses 128-bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) web technology to encrypt all shared data. This means that all your personal information and credit card numbers are protected while it is being sent over the Internet.7\. Consent

By using the 

Badr Ailrlines website, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Badr Ailrlines in the ways described above. If you have any further questions about our Privacy Policy or its implementation, please contact our customer relations department at [CRM@badrairlines.com](mailto:CRM@badrairlines.com) or call us on (1111). 

Any changes to the privacy policy will be posted on this page.
